<blog>
   <post>
      <title> Easter Sunday </title>
      <date>April 18, 2020</date>
      <author> Keith Taylor</author>
      <summary>
	  <image_path>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1LRGQkAU5rqgEC18u7aULdBHlL8gZe4u1/view?usp=sharing </image_path>
	  <text>
		A Christian festival and cultural holiday commemorating the resurrection of Jesus from the dead.</text>
	   </summary>
	  <body>
	  This is the Sunday before Easter Sunday. It is the first day of Holy Week and celebrates Jesus's arrival in Jerusalem riding on a donkey. Crowds of people came out of the city to greet him, throwing down palm branches on the road.
      Anglican and Roman Catholic churches give out small crosses made from palm leaves, as a reminder of Jesus's entrance into Jerusalem and his death on the cross. Some Christians keep these in their homes all year as a symbol of their faith.
	  Many churches hold special services on Easter Sunday, which celebrate the Jesus Christ's resurrection after his crucifixion. Many people also decorate eggs. These can be hard boiled eggs that can be eaten later, but may also be model eggs made of plastic, chocolate, candy or other materials. 
	  It is also common to organize Easter egg hunts. Eggs of some form are hidden, supposedly by a rabbit or hare. People, especially children, then search for them. In some areas, Easter egg hunts are a popular way for local businesses to promote themselves or may even be organized by churches.
	  
	  </body>
    </post>
	  
	<post>
      <title> Diwali </title>
      <date>July 11, 2020</date>
      <author> Pankaj Talukder </author>
      <summary>
	  <image_path> https://drive.google.com/file/d/1zH7c6oXE_N1gyet-whlfj-kUZaJvRgHw/view?usp=sharing</image_path>
		<text>
		Diwali is a festival of lights and one of the major festivals celebrated by Hindus, Buddhists, Jains, and Sikhs. </text>
	   </summary>
	  <body>
	   Diwali, also spelled Divali, one of the major religious festivals in Hinduism, Jainism, and Sikhism, lasting for five days from the 13th day of the dark half of the lunar month Ashvina to the second day of the light half of the lunar month Karttika.
	   (The corresponding dates in the Gregorian calendar usually fall in late October and November.) The name is derived from the Sanskrit term dipavali, meaning “row of lights.” The festival generally symbolizes the victory of light over darkness.
	   Observances of Diwali differ depending on region and tradition. Among Hindus the most widespread custom is the lighting of diyas (small earthenware lamps filled with oil) on the night of the new moon to invite the presence of Lakshmi, the goddess of wealth. 
	   In Bengal the goddess Kali is worshipped. In North India the festival also celebrates the royal homecoming of Rama (along with Sita, Lakshmana, and Hanuman) to the city of Ayodhya after defeating Ravana, the 10-headed king of the demons, thus connecting the festival with the holiday of Dussehra.
	   In South India the festival marks Krishna’s defeat of the demon Narakasura. Some celebrate Diwali as a commemoration of the marriage of Lakshmi and Vishnu, while others observe it as the birthday of Lakshmi.
	  </body>
    </post>  
	  
	<post>
      <title> Eid-Al-Fitr</title>
      <date> July 27, 2021 </date>
      <author> Rokibul Hasan </author>
      <summary>
	  <image_path>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1pbh1xKi_5Rb_b0v0_cMZCLJK_zRLFZCW/view?usp=sharing </image_path>
		<text>
		 The religious holiday is celebrated by Muslims worldwide because it marks the end of the month-long dawn-to-sunset fasting of Ramadan.</text>
	   </summary>
	  <body>
	  Eid al-Fitr has a particular salat (Islamic prayer) that consists of two rakats (units) generally performed in an open field or large hall. It may only be performed in congregation and features six additional Takbirs (raising of the hands to the ears while saying "Allāhu ʾAkbar", meaning "God is the greatest") in the Hanafi school of Sunni Islam: three at the start of the first rakat and three just before ruku in the second rakat.
	  Other Sunni schools usually have 12 Takbirs, similarly split in groups of seven and five. In Shia Islam, the salat has six Takbirs in the first rakat at the end of qira'a, before ruku, and five in the second. Depending on the juristic opinion of the locality, this salat is either fard (فرض, obligatory), mustahabb (strongly recommended) or mandūb (مندوب, preferable). After the salat, Muslims celebrate the Eid al-Fitr in various ways with food ("Eid cuisine") being a central theme, which also gives the holiday the nickname "Sweet Eid" or "Sugar Feast".
	  </body>
    </post>  
	  	  	  
</blog>